International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5676
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 72 (Washington, D.C.), 1936-1954 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Local 72 (Washington, D.C.), 1937-1941 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Local 73 (Flemington, New Jersey), 1938-1941 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Local 73 (Flemington, New Jersey), 1939-1941 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Local 74 (Chicago, Illinois), 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Local 75 (Atlantic City, New Jersey), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Local 75 (Atlantic City, New Jersey), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Local 75 (Atlantic City, New Jersey), 1926-1947 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Local 75 (Atlantic City, New Jersey), 1939-1941 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Local 77 (New York, New York), 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Local 77 (New York, New York), 1936-1939 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Local 78 (Rochester, New York), 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Local 78 (Rochester, New York), 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  correspondence re Oakland Fur Workers contract and strike; newsletters; by-lays of Local 79; correspondence re strike against Fred Benioff; articles, correspondence re organizing in Seattle and AFL's attempt to split the Seattle local, 1937; membership list; and routine.
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1938 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  membership list; official ballot; and routine correspondence.
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1940 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1941 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1942 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1947-1954 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  correspondence between Gold and local members re problems in the local, 3 p.; lack of interest among members in the local, "slowly dying".
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1936-1941 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Local 79 (San Francisco, California), 1936-1941 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Local 80 (Bronx, New York), 1936 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Local 80 (Bronx, New York), 1937 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  correspondence re merging of Rabbit Fur Dyers; handwritten lists (?); broadside; sample ballot; membership list; and routine.
- Local 80 (Bronx, New York), 1938 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  membership lists and routine.
- Local 80 (New York City, New York), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  membership lists; lists of members dropped; and routine.
- Local 80 (New York City, New York), 1940 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  lists of members and routine.
- Local 80 (New York City, New York), 1941-1945 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  membership lists; information re dropped, withdrawn and reinstated members; and routine correspondence.
- Local 80 (New York City, New York), 1936-1942 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Local 80 (New York City, New York), 1936-1942 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Locals 80 and 88 (New York City, New York), 1937-1940 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  list of members; financial statements; and routine correspondence.
- Locals 80 and 88 (New York City, New York), 1937-1940 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Local 84 (New Haven, Connecticut), 1937-1938 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Local 84 (New Haven, Connecticut), 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Local 84 (New Haven, Connecticut), 1941 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  correspondence re sending strike benefit funds to the local and being excused from picketing because of extreme heat and a holiday.
- Local 84 (New Haven, Connecticut), 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  financial statements and routine.
- Local 84 (New Haven, Connecticut), 1938-1940 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  correspondence re member complaint about being transferred from one shop to another; problems re organizing out-of-town shops; list of union shops; and routine.
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1937 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  correspondence re shops organized and wages being paid, etc.; membership list; official ballot; and routine.
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1938 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  membership list and routine.
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  membership lists and routine correspondence.
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1940 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  membership lists; financial statements; and routine correspondence.
- Local 85 (New York City, New York), 1936-1942 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1936 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  handwritten financial report for 1935; need for financial assistance for organizing; broadsides; Lucchi makes suggestions to business agent re organizing activities; legal document (petition for injunction); and routine.
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1936 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  strike against Fox Co.; legal document; receipts; organizer describes mass demonstration, etc. against Fox Co.; strike at Higbee Co.; and routine.
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1936 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  re strike continues at Higbee Co.; other strikes, organizing; membership list; correspondence re agreements settled; leaflet re I. J. Fox Co.; re arrangement for educational program through teachers union, for members; newspaper clippings re organizing drive; audit report; program of "Victory Banquet"; and routine.
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1937 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  membership list; correspondence re forming a strike committee; organizing, etc.; and routine.
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1938-1940 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1945-1951 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  audit reports; correspondence re problems in Midwest District; 8/13/47 letter to Gold from Business Manager re employer hiring a black worker; routine.
- Local 86 (Cleveland, Ohio), 1936-1943 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  includes "Minutes of the Pacific Coast District Council," 4 p., 3/21/36; financial reports; correspondence re strike and settlement with Wholesale Association, 1936; correspondence re injunction against the union by Maurice Ball Fur Co., 1936-37; reports of Local 87 activities; correspondence re contracting problem, 1945; correspondence re merger with MCBW, 1954; and routine correspondence.
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Local 87 (Los Angeles, California), 1936-1940 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1926-1942 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  formerly South Norwalk, Connecticut; resolution re dissolution of Local 88, 1928; membership lists.
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1926-1942 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1926-1942 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1926-1942 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1926-1942 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1926-1942 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Local 88 (New York, New York), 1937-1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Local 89 (Union City, New Jersey), 1936-1947 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  includes arbitration award; correspondence with Alaska Chemical Corp. re contract negotiations, 1936; correspondence re amalgamation of Local 89 with Locals 2 and 88, 1937; audit reports; and routine correspondence.
- Local 89 (Union City, New Jersey), 1936-1947 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Local 89 (Union City, New Jersey), 1936-1947 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Local 89 (Union City, New Jersey), 1936-1947 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Local 89 (Union City, New Jersey), 1936-1941 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  extensive correspondence re organizing drive and strike 1936-37; reports on agreement with Neaman Fur Co.; extensive correspondence and court documents re injunction against local; broadsides; resolution; membership lists; articles; financial statements; correspondence re relationship with Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1945; and routine.
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Local 91 (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1926-1945 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Local 92 (Providence, Rhode Island), 1939-1947 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Local 92 (Providence, Rhode Island), 1939-1947 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Local 92 (Providence, Rhode Island), 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Local 94 (Duluth, Minnesota), 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Local 94 (Duluth, Minnesota), 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Local 94 (Duluth, Minnesota), 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Local 94 (Duluth, Minnesota), 1937-1941 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Local 95 (Hartford, Connecticut), 1934-1941 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Local 95 (Hartford, Connecticut), 1934-1941 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Local 95 (Hartford, Connecticut), 1936-1940 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Local 96 (Detroit, Michigan), 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Local 97 (Salamanca, New York), 1942 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  routine correspondence
- Local 98 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1937-1941 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  includes membership list; financial statements; and routine correspondence.
- Local 99 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1937-1938 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  lists of membership and routine.
- Local 99 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1939 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Local 99 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1940 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Local 99 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1941 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Local 99 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1942-1947 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Local 99 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1937-1942 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Local 100 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1936-1942 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  membership list; letter from member complaining about Max Federman and his associates discriminating against union members; and routine.
- Local 100 (Toronto, Ontario, Canada), 1936-1942 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Local 101 (New York City, New York), 1939-1942 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  letters of member certification; and routine.
- Local 105 (New York City, New York), 1937-1942 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  letters of membership certification; handwritten death claims; and routine.
- Local 110 (New York City, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  letters of membership certification.
- Local 115 (New York City, New York), 1936-1942 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  letters of membership certification and routine.
- Local 118 (Newark, New Jersey), 1938-1941 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  routine and financial.
- Local 120 (New York City, New York), 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  ballot, list of members and routine.
- Local 120 (New York City, New York), 1940 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Local 120 (New York City, New York), 1941 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Local 120 (New York City, New York), 1942 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Local 120 (New York City, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1937 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  correspondence re resolution for issuing charter for Chauffeurs and Helpers; official ballot; and routine.
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1938 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  sample ballot; correspondence re dropped members; re financial support for American Labor Party; and routine.
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1939 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1940 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  list of members; and routine.
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1941 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1942 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  list of members and routine.
- Local 122 (New York City, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  financial.
- Local 125 (New York City, New York), 1937-1938 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  correspondence re forming 2 locals out of Local 125; list of transfers; and routine.
- Local 125 (New York City, New York), 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  membership and "drop" lists; and routine.
- Local 125 (New York City, New York), 1941 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  15 p. "Minutes of a Conference Between Representatives of the International Ladies Handbag, Pocketbook and Novelty Workers and Internation Fur and Leather Workers," re jurisdictional disputes; and routine.
- Local 125 (New York City, New York), 1942-1945 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  lists of members; routine.
- Local 125 (New York City, New York), 1937-1942 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Local 130 (Long Branch, New Jersey), 1937 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  lists of members; and routine.
- Local 130 (Long Branch, New Jersey), 1938-1940 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Local 130 (Long Branch, New Jersey), 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Local 130 (Long Branch, New Jersey), 1937-1942 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1937 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1938 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1939 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  re dropped and suspended members and routine.
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1940 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1941 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  sample ballot; lists of members; and routine.
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1942-1947 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  letter from Lucchi to local re mass meeting and support of Roosevelt; list of members; letter to Gold from local re finding employment for two veterans; correspondence from A. Hollander and Son employees; 3 p. letter from Gold to President of local re problems within local - anti-Semitic acts.
- Local 135 (Middletown, New York), 1937-1942 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  financial reports.
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  includes membership lists; correspondence re negotiations with A. Hollander, 1945; correspondence with the International re problems with Locals 2 and 3, 1954; and routine correspondence.
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1954 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1954 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1954 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1954 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1954 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Local 140 (Newark, New Jersey), 1937-1942 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Local 145 (Yonkers, New York), 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  includes membership lists; financial reports; "Progress in Negotiations for Affiliation of United Mechanics Local 150 with the Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Union," 6 p., no date; and routine correspondence.
- Local 145 (Yonkers, New York), 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Local 145 (Yonkers, New York), 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Local 145 (Yonkers, New York), 1938-1945 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Local 150 (New York, New York), 1938-1947 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  includes membership lists; letter re Local 150 affiliating with Joint Board, 10/29/47; news release; financial statements; and routine correspondence.
- Local 150 (New York, New York), 1938-1947 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Local 150 (New York, New York), 1938-1947 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Local 150 (New York, New York), 1938-1947 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Local 150 (New York, New York), 1938-1940 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Local 155 (New York, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  includes membership list; and routine correspondence.
- Local 155 (New York, New York), 1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Local 155 (New York, New York), 1939-1942 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Local 160 (New York, New York), 1939-1941 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Local 165 (New York, New York), 1941 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Local 196 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1947-1951 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Local 700 (Merry Point, Virginia), 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  press release; report of local activities; and routine correspondence.
- Local 20 (Lynn, Massachusetts), 1945-1955 (Box 27a, Folder 1)
  report of activities; routine correspondence.
- Local 20 (Lynn, Massachusetts), 1945-1955 (Box 27a, Folder 2)
- Local 21 (Peabody, Massachusetts), 1945 (Box 27a, Folder 3)
  by-laws, radio address by Ben Gold (11 p.) and article (7 p.) re voting to maintain Locals 21 and 22's affiliation with IFLWU; and routine correspondence.
- Local 27 (Newark, New Jersey), 1940-1945 (Box 27a, Folder 4)
- Local 27 (Newark, New Jersey), 1940-1945 (Box 27a, Folder 5)
- Local 29 (Girard, Ohio), 1945 (Box 27a, Folder 6)
  resolution on espionage and report; correspondence re work stoppage at Ohio Leather Plant Co.
- Local 30 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1940-1947 (Box 27a, Folder 7)
- Local 30 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1940-1947 (Box 27a, Folder 8)
- Local 31 (Curwensville, Pennsylvania), 1941-1942 (Box 27a, Folder 9)
  agreement between Local 31 and Franklin Tanning Co., 1941; routine correspondence; and financial statement.
- Local 34 (Hoboken, New Jersey), 1945-1947 (Box 27a, Folder 10)
- Local 35 (Brooklyn, New York), 1940-1947 (Box 27a, Folder 11)
  correspondence and supplemental agreement with Brightman Leather Co.; routine correspondence.
- Local 37 (Elkland, Pennsylvania), 1941-1942 (Box 27a, Folder 12)
- Local 39 (Buffalo, New York), 1942 (Box 27a, Folder 13)
- Local 43 (Chicago, Illinois), 1941-1942 (Box 27a, Folder 14)
  extensive correspondence re Local 43 raiding the International Ladies' Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union, Locals 44 and 50; and routine correspondence.
- Local 44 (Gowanda, New York), 1941-1942 (Box 27a, Folder 15)
- Local 44 (Gowanda, New York), 1941-1942 (Box 27a, Folder 16)
- Local 46 (Worcester, Massachusetts), Local 47, 1942-1955 (Box 27a, Folder 17)
- Local 60 (St. Louis, Missouri), Local 82 (Ridgeway, Pennsylvania), Local 83 (Wilcox, Pennsylvania), 1942-1945 (Box 27a, Folder 18)
- Local 201 (Wilmington, Delaware), Local 202 (Gloversville, New York), 1942-1945 (Box 27a, Folder 19)
  correspondence re jurisdictional question between Local 202 and International Ladies' Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union; and routine correspondence.
- Local 204 (Waukegan, Illinois), Local 206 (Camden, New Jersey), Local 208 (Easton, Pennsylvania), 1941-1947 (Box 27a, Folder 20)
- Local 211 (Williamsport, Pennsylvania), 1942 (Box 27a, Folder 21)
- Local 213 (Los Angeles, California), 1942 (Box 27a, Folder 22)
- Local 214 (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1945 (Box 27a, Folder 23)
  reports of activities.
- Local 216 (Clearfield, Pennsylvania), 1941-1942 (Box 27a, Folder 24)
- Local 230 (Richmond, Virginia), Local 245 (Boyne City, Michigan) - report of activities (Local 230); and routine correspondence, 1941- 1945 (Box 27a, Folder 25)
- Local 265 (Luray, Virginia), 1942-1948 (Box 27a, Folder 26)
  minutes of Local meetings; membership list; correspondence re War Labor Board's handling of wage increase question; Leather Division rules covering Death Benefit Fund, 1 p., no date.
- Local 265 (Luray, Virginia), 1942-1948 (Box 27a, Folder 27)
- Local 265 (Luray, Virginia), 1942-1948 (Box 27a, Folder 28)
- Local 270 (Lowell, Massachusetts), 1945 (Box 27a, Folder 29)
  correspondence and agreement with American Hide and Leather Co.
- Local 285 (Endicott, New York), 1944-1947 (Box 27a, Folder 30)
  agreement with Endicott-Johnson Corp., 1944-47; report on union status of U. S. Hoffman Machinery Co. in Syracuse, New York; correspondence re Johnson City division of Endicott-Johnson Fire Prevention Department not being covered by the agreement; correspondence re AFL's role in splitting the local at Endicott-Johnson; scattered issues of Endicott Leather Worker; "E-J Workers Special Bulletin."
- Local 310 (Ashland, Kentucky); Local 335 (Red Wing, Minnesota); Local 340 (Alpena, Michigan); Local 350 (Williamsport, Maryland); Local 370 (Richmond, Virginia), 1945 (Box 27a, Folder 31)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 32)
  extensive correspondence re organizing Local 485; establishment of the local and negotiations with West Hickory Tanning Co. as well as articles, agreements, handwritten notes, broadsides; extensive correspondence re United Leather Workers International Union, AFL, raiding Local 485; grievance reports; court document; form letters; court exhibits in libel case United Leather Workers International Union, AFL vs. IFLWU, CIO, 9/48; proposed agreement clauses.
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 33)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 34)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 35)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 36)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 37)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 38)
- Local 485 (West Hickory, Pennsylvania), 1947-1952 (Box 27a, Folder 39)
- Locals General, 1927-1954 (Box 27a, Folder 40)
  includes copies of routine form letters covering many topics.
- Locals General, 1927-1954 (Box 27a, Folder 41)
- Canada - District Council 10, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  extensive detailed correspondence between Gold, Feinglass, and Robert Haddow, President, re Canadian legislation re labor bills and the effect it will make on District 10; re contents of a new agreement; re District 10 setting up a retirement fund for officers; re general state of affairs (letters from Gold) in the U. S.; District 10 struggle with AFL; merger with Meat Cutters; broadside and release re merger with Meat Cutters; and misc.
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  January to May; correspondence between Albert Roy, M. Kaufman, Charles Stetsky, and Andrew Wenneis re agreement with Fur Manufacturers Protective Association; Montreal situation, firm of Kaufman in particular, trying to force workers to sign individual agreements; re general strike; copy of agreement and broadsides.
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  June to December; correpondence re finances for general strike in Montreal; resolutions adopted by strikers; re New York Joint Board using sabotaging tactics. Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  between Gold, Schactman and Roy re reports on general situation in Montreal; and routine.
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Canada - Montreal, Joint Board of, 1945-1954 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  correspondence between Gold, Charlotte Gauthier and W. Couturier re workers requesting holidays from Hollander Co.; expiration of contracts; and routine.
- Canada - Toronto Fur Workers Union Joint Board, 1924-1936 (Box 28, Folder 11)